(Raj:)Sheldon,
we've been on this train 90 seconds...
(Leonard:)...and you've already said
a thousand words.
(Leonard:)Just tell us where to sit and shut up.
(Sheldon(ripping off sticker):)Here.
(Sheldon:)I'm hoping once you reap
the endorphic rewards...
(Sheldon:)...of the steady clickety-clack
of steel wheels on polished rails...
(Sheldon:)- ...your sour disposition will abate.
- Yeah, maybe.
(Leonard:)Back in the 21st century, people are raising
tray tables and putting seat-backs upright...
...because it's time to land
in San Francisco.
(Raj:)It's not so bad really.
At least these trains have modern plumbing.
(Raj:)In India, you squat over a hole in the train
and expose your naked buttocks...
(Raj:)...to the chilly air of Rajasthan.
(Sheldon:)He is referring, of course, to third class...
(Sheldon:)...on Indian Railways' magnificent
Ranakpur Express...
...and its 1200-kilometer journey
from Maharashtra to the Bikaner Junction.
(Leonard:)Oh, look.
Now he's boring on an international scale.
Holy crap, look.
- Is that who I think it is?
- It can't be.